sbglobal.info 2017-03-31

# privacy policy

## Privacy Policy

SB Global Infosoft respects your privacy and are committed to protecting personal information that you may share with us. This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect and use your personal information.

##### Information We Collect :

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, occupation, industry, personal interests, and other information when needed to provide a service or product or carry out a transaction you have requested. Unless you choose to voluntarily provide the information to us, we do not collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number, fax number, or e-mail address. For instance, you may be asked to provide us with your personal information when you fill the required fields for requesting a Pre-SEO Analysis Report or a Contact Us form. If you elect to submit any personal information, your submission is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you consent to such terms. 

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the SB Global Infosoft website. On some pages, you can make requests, register to receive materials, and use free webmaster tools. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: Name   
Company name  
Address   
Email address   
Phone number   
Web address   
About Your Competitor 

##### Log Files:

Like many other Web sites, www.Sbglobal.info makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

##### Cookies :

Like many other commercial websites, the SB Global Infosoft website may use standard technologies, such as "cookies" and other HTML tools, to collect information about how you use the site or to record that you opened an email marketing message. As such, we may log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there.

Some parts of the SB Global Infosoft website use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information. A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies too. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www. Sbglobal.info sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

SB Global Infosoft has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. SB Global Infosoft's privacy policy does not apply to, and have no control over the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of the SB Global Infosoft website if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our website. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to certain of SB Global Infosoft's web pages that require a login and password. 

##### Notice :

SB Global Infosoft will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the section entitled "Information Sharing and Disclosure" below. In most cases we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in" prior to receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we will require your affirmative action to indicate your consent before we use your information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted. At a minimum, we will always give you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving such materials. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by clicking or checking the appropriate option or box at the point of collection. 

##### How We Use Information Collected :

SB Global Infosoft uses personal information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers or other information we think you would like to hear about either from us or from our business partners, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research 

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure :

##### Data Security :

SB Global Infosoft and its companies are committed to protecting your personal information and do so with certain physical and technological procedures. However, we cannot ensure the security of the information as you transmit it to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. This includes using a secure browser where applicable.

##### Links :

SB Global Infosoft website may provide links to other World Wide Web sites or resources. Because SB Global Infosoft has no control over such sites and resources, you acknowledge and agree that SB Global Infosoft is not responsible for the availability of such external sites or resources, and does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, or other materials on or available from such sites or resources. You further acknowledge and agree that SB Global Infosoft shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with use of or reliance on any such Content, goods or services available on or through any such site or resource. You should separately check the Privacy Policy Statements of the respective websites. 

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy :

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. We may also, but are not required to, notify you by email or regular mail.
